studiesweekly.com 2014-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Studies Weekly

## Privacy Policy

 **What information do we collect?** We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey.  
    When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or school name. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

**What do we use your information for?  ** Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

 **Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?  ** We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.   
    We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.   
    After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.  
     **Do we use cookies?  ** Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
    We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.  
     **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  ** We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
     **Third party links  ** Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Limited Permission to Reprint and Distribute**

 **Grantor  ** American Legacy Publishing is the creator of Studies Weekly publications, educational materials designed for use in classrooms and home schools in the United States. Studies Weekly publications are protected by U.S. Copyright Law, Title 17 of the U.S. Code.  
 **     Publications Covered under this Limited Permission** This Limited Permission document applies to all Studies Weekly publications, including discontinued publications, publications currently in print and all future Studies Weekly publications.  
 **     Grantees** Permission to reprint and distribute is granted solely to teachers who have a current and up-to-date subscription for a Studies Weekly publication. Teachers with current and up-to-date subscriptions are hereafter known as SUBSCRIBERS. Publications to which SUBSCRIBERS are subscribed are hereafter known as SUBSCRIBED PUBLICATIONS.  
 **     Purpose of the Agreement** The purpose of this agreement is to allow limited reprint and distribution of Studies Weekly publications for the convenience of SUBSCRIBERS and their registered students. It does NOT allow for reprinting and distribution beyond the number of registered students or for use in classrooms other than that of the SUBSCRIBER. SUBSCRIBERS are strictly prohibited from reprinting multiple copies for the purpose of distribution to students of non-subscribers.  
 **     Reprint/Distribution Scope and Limitations** This Limited Permission agreement applies to student editions, teacher editions and any supplemental materials - both in print and online - included with the SUBSCRIBED PUBLICATION.  
    SUBSCRIBERS may reprint and distribute single copies of the SUBSCRIBED PUBLICATION only to students officially enrolled in her or his class or to students participating in home schools that comply with state and local guidelines SUBSCRIBERS must register students who may receive single-copy reprints of the SUBSCRIBED PUBLICATION at www.estudiesweekly.com as soon after the beginning of the school year as is practicable. When new students are added to the class over the course of the school year, SUBSCRIBERS must register those students at www.estudiesweekly.com as soon after enrollment as is practicable. The number of subscriptions a SUBSCRIBER has to a publication MUST correlate to the number of students registered in the SUBSCRIBER’S class.  
    Permission to reprint and distribute is limited solely to the SUBSCRIBED PUBLICATION and is strictly limited to the school year for which the subscription was purchased. Example: A subscription for the 2013-2014 school year may only be distributed to registered students during the 2013-2014 school year.  
    Permission to reprint and distribute is NOT granted for school, class, teacher, student or any other websites. SUBSCRIBERS who wish to make publications available for online viewing to parents and students during the subscription year must register students at www.estudiesweekly.com.  
    Permission to reprint and distribute is NOT granted for commercial purposes of any kind. Any reprint or distribution for commercial purposes is strictly prohibited.  
    Permission to reprint and distribute is NOT granted to any person who is not a SUBSCRIBER, as described above. Any reprinting or distribution by any person who is not a SUBSCRIBER and distribution to non-registered students are expressly prohibited.  
    Any questions regarding this Limited Permission may be sent to service@studiesweekly.com.  
 **     California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance** Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.  
 **     Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance** We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  
 **     Online Privacy Policy Only** This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  
 **     Your Consent** By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.  
 **     Changes to our Privacy Policy** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on June 9, 2011.  
 **     Contacting Us** If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.studiesweekly.com  
1922 West 200 North, Lindon, Utah 84042 / USA  
orders@studiesweekly.com  
866-311-8734
